♪ DECIDE YOURSELF IF
RADIO'S GONNA STAY ♪
♪ REASON IT COULD
POLISH UP THE GRAY ♪
♪ PUT THAT, PUT THAT,
PUT THAT UP YOUR WALL ♪
♪ THAT THIS ISN'T
COUNTRY AT ALL ♪
♪ RADIO STATION ♪
♪ DECIDE YOURSELF ♪
♪ CALLING OUT IN TRANSIT ♪
♪ RADIO FREE EUROPE ♪
♪ RADIO ♪
♪ DECIDE DEFY THE
MEDIA TOO FAST ♪
♪ INSTEAD OF PUSHIN'
PALACES TO FALL ♪
♪ PUT THAT, PUT THAT,
PUT THAT BEFORE ALL ♪
♪ THAT THIS ISN'T
FORTUNATE AT ALL ♪
♪ RADIO STATION ♪
♪ DECIDE YOURSELF ♪
♪ CALLING OUT IN TRANSIT ♪
♪ RADIO FREE EUROPE ♪
♪ RADIO ♪
♪ DECIDE YOURSELF ♪
♪ COME IN ON A BOAT ♪
♪ MEDIA'S TOO FAST ♪
♪ KEEP ME OUT OF
COUNTRY AND THE WORD ♪
♪ DISAPPOINTERS INTO US ABSURD ♪
♪ STRAIGHT OFF THE BOAT ♪
♪ WHERE TO GO ♪
♪ CALLING OUT IN TRANSIT ♪
♪ RADIO FREE EUROPE ♪